[{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664110113,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":9631,"timeElapsed":145424},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664122870,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":12755,"timeElapsed":158182},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664133182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":10310,"timeElapsed":168494},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664136219,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3033,"timeElapsed":171531},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664145717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":9496,"timeElapsed":181029},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664153533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":7814,"timeElapsed":188845},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664157607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":4071,"timeElapsed":192919},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664162659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5050,"timeElapsed":197971},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664165959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3296,"timeElapsed":201270},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664175197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":7345,"timeElapsed":210509},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664181986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":6786,"timeElapsed":217298},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664188015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":6026,"timeElapsed":223327},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664195550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":7533,"timeElapsed":230862},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664199714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4161,"timeElapsed":235025},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664205146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5430,"timeElapsed":240458},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664209074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3926,"timeElapsed":244386},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664212727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3650,"timeElapsed":248039},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664214960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2229,"timeElapsed":250272},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664224654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":8147,"timeElapsed":259966},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664229696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5041,"timeElapsed":265008},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664235630,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5931,"timeElapsed":270942},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664239749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4115,"timeElapsed":275061},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664246936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":7184,"timeElapsed":282248},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664249734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2795,"timeElapsed":285046},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664253197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3459,"timeElapsed":288509},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664257584,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4384,"timeElapsed":292896},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664259709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2122,"timeElapsed":295021},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664269699,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":8418,"timeElapsed":305010},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664272798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3095,"timeElapsed":308110},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664276940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":4138,"timeElapsed":312252},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664279561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2618,"timeElapsed":314872},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664282868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3304,"timeElapsed":318180},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664284798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1927,"timeElapsed":320110},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664289109,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4308,"timeElapsed":324421},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664291509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2397,"timeElapsed":326821},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664293626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2114,"timeElapsed":328938},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664300489,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6859,"timeElapsed":335801},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664308710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6547,"timeElapsed":344021},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664311242,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2529,"timeElapsed":346554},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664315364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4120,"timeElapsed":350675},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664317445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2079,"timeElapsed":352757},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664320673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3226,"timeElapsed":355985},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664322615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1938,"timeElapsed":357926},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664326690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4071,"timeElapsed":362002},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664329134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2441,"timeElapsed":364446},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664332451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3315,"timeElapsed":367763},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664336599,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4145,"timeElapsed":371911},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664345017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6814,"timeElapsed":380329},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664347114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2095,"timeElapsed":382426},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664351564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4447,"timeElapsed":386876},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664353268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1701,"timeElapsed":388579},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664358061,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4790,"timeElapsed":393372},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664360839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2775,"timeElapsed":396151},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664365658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4816,"timeElapsed":400970},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664367858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2196,"timeElapsed":403170},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664370030,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2167,"timeElapsed":405342},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664376636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5402,"timeElapsed":411948},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664378524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1884,"timeElapsed":413836},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664380765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2237,"timeElapsed":416077},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664382600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1831,"timeElapsed":417912},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664386201,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3598,"timeElapsed":421513},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664389389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3185,"timeElapsed":424701},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664393122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3729,"timeElapsed":428434},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664395497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2373,"timeElapsed":430809},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664398063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2564,"timeElapsed":433375},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664405698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5487,"timeElapsed":441010},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664407489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1788,"timeElapsed":442801},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664410727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3236,"timeElapsed":446039},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664412258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1528,"timeElapsed":447570},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664415190,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2929,"timeElapsed":450502},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664417791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2599,"timeElapsed":453102},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664422539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":4745,"timeElapsed":457850},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664425022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2480,"timeElapsed":460333},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664429058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4033,"timeElapsed":464369},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664436449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5733,"timeElapsed":471761},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664438110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1658,"timeElapsed":473422},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664440049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1936,"timeElapsed":475360},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664442071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2019,"timeElapsed":477383},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664445452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3378,"timeElapsed":480764},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664448050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2596,"timeElapsed":483362},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664450623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2571,"timeElapsed":485935},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664453622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2995,"timeElapsed":488933},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664456789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3164,"timeElapsed":492101},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664464149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5762,"timeElapsed":499461},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664466761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2608,"timeElapsed":502073},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664469079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2315,"timeElapsed":504391},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664471089,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2007,"timeElapsed":506401},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664475045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3953,"timeElapsed":510357},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664476816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1767,"timeElapsed":512128},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664480563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3743,"timeElapsed":515875},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664483171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2605,"timeElapsed":518483},{"subjectID":"vbn5ty7wad","prolificID":"5967e9a831394d0001abdb3f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421558a5eab6359e3707b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664485227,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2052,"timeElapsed":520539}]